Stevens-Cogdell-Sanders-Venning collection LCP.Stevens
Library Company of Philadelphia
- Series V. Unattributed family papers
  - [Venning family papers?]: Miscellaneous papers, 1890, undated (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - [Unknown owner]: Common Prayer book, 1892 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - [Unknown owner]: Common Prayer book, 1892 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - [Unknown owner]: Pocket New Testament League, circa 1914 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Anonymous: Current opinion for July: "Are We Menaced by a New Race War", circa 1915 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - [Unknown owner]: Address book listing Richard Chew and three others, undated (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - [Unknown owner]: Autograph Album, "Your Hidden Skeleton", 1910 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - [Venning family papers?]: Business cards, undated (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - [Unknown owner]: Daily Journal, 1935 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - [Unknown owner]: "Minutes on Some Passages from Dr. [Smith's] book on [illegible], undated (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - [Unknown owner]: Poem, "Spring Flowers", undated (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Series VI. Scrapbook materials and related ephemera
  - Invitation for St. Valentine's Convivial Association Ball; Boston Herald newspaper clipping; program for Grand Concert at Musical Fund Hall, 1851, 1918 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Scrapbook page with newspaper clippings and Union Building and Loan Association officer list, circa 1860 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Program for Airiolean Quartette Glee Club event, 1871 March 13 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Scrapbook page with program for Amphion Choral Society's First Public Rehearsal, a Valentine note and a Christmas card, 1876 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Broadside and program for events with the Sabbath School and the Sons of St. Thomas Society of St. Thomas P.E. Church, 1877 May 30, 1908 April 24 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Ticket to Mr. C. Samuel Adger for "A Concert and Literary Entertainment" given at Y.M.U.B. Hall in San Francisco, 1879 October 9 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Broadside for operetta by the pupils of Miss Laney's Industrial School at the Market Hall, circa 1880 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Church of the Crucifixion Young People's Association handbills, programs and broadside, 1881-1883 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Program for Quaker City Circle's Closing Exercises music event, 1883 May 26 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Central Presbyterian Church newspaper and music programs, 1884 November 27, 1890 January (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Broadside for Pinafore at Musical Fund Hall, 1884 December 26 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Programs for concerts by students of House of Refuge, 1885 March 3, 1885 November 25 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Programs for Academy of Music's Great Star Concert featuring Dungee Troubadour Quartette and Amphion Singing Association, 1885 March 31 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Broadside for South Street Baptist Mission's Grand Complimentary Concert tendered to Mr. Phillip W. Hutchins, 1885 May 28 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Program for Lincoln University's Alumni Association Annual Meeting, 1885 June 5 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Program for Public School #16 graduation, 1885 June 30 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Bachelor-Benedict Club event invitations, 1897 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Broadside for concert at Murray A.M.E Church, 1898 May 5 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Programs for Philadelphia High School for Girls Commencement Exercises, 1898 June 15, 1905 June 16 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Invitation to Miss Meta Vaux Warrick farewell reception, invitation to Miss Venning, "The Misses Smith," and business card for Dr. Seymour De W. Ludlum's Psychopathic Hospital, 1899 September 28, 1909 January 1, undated (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Scrapbook pages regarding the Venning family, circa 1903-1910 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Programs for Philadelphia Treble-Clef Mandolin and Guitar Club concerts, 1904 May 20, 1906 April 17 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Century of the Fellowship Society broadside, 1904 October 12 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Scrapbook pages about the Venning family, 1886, 1904 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Invitations, 1906-1908 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Scrapbook pages about the Venning family, mid-19th century, 1897, 1899, 1906-1913 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Newspaper clippings and accounting information, circa 1907 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Invitation for First Public Rehearsal of the piano pupils of Miss Lillie G. Capps, 1908 June 23 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Program for Song Revue "Who is She?" at the St. Peter's Claver's Auditorium; Invitation for Auxiliary of Day Nursery, 9th annual charity ball, 1908 November 25; 1914 April 30 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Program for Association for the Protection of Colored Women's "A Dream of the Orient", 1909 May 11 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - American Negro Historical Society Memorial Meetings in honor of Robert Jones and Theophilus J. Minton, Esq., 1909 May 26 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Program for Mercy Hospital School for Nurses' First Commencement, 1909 June 3 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Programs for Mary Saunders Patterson musical events, 1909 December 30, 1918 May 31 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Citizens Republican Club programs for Soap Box Social Events, 1911-1922 (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Programs for Mendelssohn Musical Association of Philadelphia's Second Annual Concert, 1913 February 3 (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Program of Institutional Relief Organization's "International Congress of Women in Pantomime", 1919 December 5 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Program for Quaker City Beneficial Associations 35th Annual Sermon and Memorial Service, 1921 May 29 (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - Program for Commencement of the Seventh Class of South Philadelphia High School for Girls, 1921 June 20 (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - Scrapbook pages regarding the Venning Family (including obituaries and cruise information), circa 1932 (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - Program for Philippa Schuyler piano concert hosted by Associate Committee of Women, 1939 February 25 (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - Newsletter for Student Council of St. Simon the Cyrenian Church School, 1939 June (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - Programs for Constance Stokes' mezzo soprano recitals, 1939 October 19, 1941 October 17 (Box 6, Folder 49)
  - Edward W. and Edward Y. Venning, newspaper clippings and scrapbook, undated (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - Ephemera, ribbon and visiting card, undated (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - Visiting cards, undated (Box 6, Folder 52)
  - Edward W. Venning, materials, undated (Box 6, Folder 53)
  - Photocopies of newspaper clippings including articles about Jim Crow, lynching, C. Daniel Adger and Marian Anderson, circa 1900-1920 (Box 6, Folder 54)
  - Genealogical information compiled by the Library Company of Philadelphia, undated (Box 6, Folder 55)
  - Scrapbook page regarding Edward W. and Edward Y. Venning, 1862, 1869, 1906. (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Soapbox Social financial reports, 1911, 1912. (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Obituary for Ada "Bricktop" Smith, circa 1984. (Box 9, Folder 18)
- Series VII. Hinkson family papers [12142.F, 12143.F], Bulk, 1954-1960; 1929-1982
  - Hinkson, Cordelia: Correspondence from Pearl Buck, copy of Pearl Buck's "The Dark Shadow," and articles and letters regarding "The Dark Shadow,", 1942-1964 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Hinkson, DeHaven: Correspondence, 1929, 1941, undated. (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Jackson, Mary Hinkson: Correspondence from the Dean of the University of Wisconsin, 6 May 1946. (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Jackson, Mary Hinkson: Correspondence to Cordelia and DeHaven Hinkson, 17 May 1954. (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Jackson, Mary Hinkson: Correspondence to Cordelia and DeHaven Hinkson, February-May 1954. (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Jackson, Mary Hinkson: Correspondence to Cordelia and DeHaven Hinkson, June-August 1954. (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Jackson, Mary Hinkson: Correspondence to Cordelia and DeHaven Hinkson, May-June 1960. (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Jackson, Mary Hinkson: Correspondence to Cordelia and DeHaven Hinkson, July 1960. (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Jackson, Mary Hinkson: Correspondence to Cordelia and DeHaven Hinkson, 1965, 1972. (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Postcards to Cordelia Hinkson, Mary Hinkson Jackson, Dede Hinkson, 1945-1982 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Alumnae Association. The Philadelphia High School for Girls: 150 Years, A Beginning, 1848-1998 [DVD] (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Photocopies of articles and notes about the Cogdell, Hinkson, and Chew families, 1959, 1967, undated. (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Obituary and eulogy for Charles Shelton Brown, April 2004. (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Group for the Advancement of Psychiatry. "Psychiatric Aspects of School Desegregation,", May 1957. (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Chew, Richard S.: Letter and articles, 1925, undated. (Box 9, Folder 15)